brilliant.co 2018-11-03

# Privacy Policy – Brilliant Bicycle Co.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Priority Outdoor Products, Inc. ("Brilliant", "Brilliant Bicycles", “we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use, disclosure, and protection of your information on www.brilliant.co (the “Site”) and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Site and the Services, through your user account on the Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.  

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**  
This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of information, including personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”), gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.   

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Services or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third-party access to your Personal Information you do so at your own risk.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

_Account Information:  _  
If you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, but only rarely when we feel such information is important. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we, regardless, reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

_Information we may receive from third parties:  _  
We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you access our Services through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by “following,” “liking,” linking your account to the Services, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to us.  This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service.  If you allow us access to your friends list, your friends’ user IDs, and your connection to those friends, may be used and stored to make your experience more social, and to allow you to invite your friends to use our Services as well as provide you with updates if and when your friends join our Services. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Services.  You may also unlink your third party account from the Services by adjusting your settings on the third party service.  If you unlink your third party account, we will remove the information collected about you in connection with that service.

_Inviting a friend to use our Services from the “Invite friends” feature:  _  
If you choose to use our invitation service to invite a third party to the Services through our “Invite friends” feature, we may collect information contained in your contact list. You understand that by inviting a friend to our Services through the “Invite friends” feature, you are directly sending a text or email from your personal accounts and that we are not storing your contact list. In addition, you understand and agree that normal carrier charges apply to communications sent from your phone. Since this invitation is coming directly from your email or phone, we do not have access to or control this communication. 

_Finding your friends on the Services:  _  
If you choose, you can locate your friends with Brilliant accounts through our “Find friends” feature. The “Find friends” feature allows you to choose to locate friends either through (i) your contact list, (ii) social media sites (such as Twitter or Facebook) or (iii) through a search of names and usernames on Brilliant. If you choose to find your friends through your contact list, then you agree to provide us access to your contact list such that we can perform the search necessary to determine whether or not someone associated with the information you provide is using our Services. If you choose to find your friends through social media sites, then you understand that the information these sites provide to us to conduct this type of search is governed by their privacy policies and your account settings on those sites. If you choose to find your friends through a search of names or usernames then simply type a name to search and see if that name or username appears on our Services.  Note that we do not retain any information contained in your contacts list, or information from social media sites about your contacts, and we do not use such information for any purpose other than to help you find your friends on our Services.

_User Content:_

Some features of the Services may allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments and photographs. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner designed to avoid revealing Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

_Financial Information:_

We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

_IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:_  
•    We may automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address and information from cookies and other technology. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on).  
•    Generally, the Services may automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner designed to identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them. 

_Email Communications:_  
We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service.

_Information Collected Using Cookies:_  
•    Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We may use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services through the Internet.   
•    Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we may use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.    
•    Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. Turning off the cookie feature may prevent you from taking advantage of some features of the Services.  
•    This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.   
Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons:   
To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties’ advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.”  Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.   
Advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personal Information (e.g., gender or age), may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.   
To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

_Aggregate Information:_  
We may collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.  
How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?

_Public Information About Your Activity on the Services:_

Some of your activity on and through the Services may be public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services.

Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. Unregistered users will not have this association, but information concerning their use of the Services (such as what pages they have visited) may be tracked anonymously through the use of cookies and stored by us. 

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.

_IP Address Information:_

While we may collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy. 

_Information You Elect to Share:_

You may access other Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Services.

_Aggregate Information:_

We may share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We may share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

_Email Communications with Us:_  
As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications relating to your Account. Communications relating to your Account will be sent only for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery.

_Financial Information:_  
As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

_Information Shared with Our Agents:  _  
We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

_Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:  _  
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others:  _  
We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

_Information We Share With Your Consent:  _  
Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

**Is Information About Me Secure?  **  
Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.  
We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.   
We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

**What Information of Mine Can I Access?**  
If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.  
California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 54 West 21st Street, Suite 404, New York NY, 10010.

**How Can I Delete My Account?  **  
Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing hello@brilliant.co. If you terminate your Account, any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your Account. However, given the nature of sharing on the Services, any activity on your Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.

**What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?**

•    You can use many of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.  
•    You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some of our features.  
•    You can delete your Account. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes, and such activity and/or information may be publicly accessible.  

**“Do Not Track”**  
Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our customers, we are not able to respond to Do-Not-Track signals from your browser at this time.  As discussed above, we track website usage information through the use of cookies for analytic and internal purposes only.  Because we do not collect this information to track you across websites over time, your selection of the “Do Not Track” option provided by your browser will not have any effect on our collection of cookie information for analytics or internal purposes.

**Children’s Privacy**  
We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as users.  The Services and their content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at hello@brilliant.co.

**What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

**What If I Have Questions or Concerns?  **  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to hello@brilliant.co. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

**Effective Date:**  March 25th, 2015
